export const  quizQuestions = [
    {
      question: 'What is the result of 15 + 7?',
      options: ['18', '22', '20', '25'],
      correctOption: '22',
    },
    {
      question: 'If 28 - 14 = X, what is the value of X?',
      options: ['14', '12', '16', '18'],
      correctOption: '14',
    },
    {
      question: 'Calculate 5 * 6.',
      options: ['30', '25', '35', '40'],
      correctOption: '30',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the sum of 42 and 19?',
      options: ['60', '61', '59', '62'],
      correctOption: '61',
    },
    {
      question: 'If Y - 8 = 15, what is the value of Y?',
      options: ['22', '23', '24', '25'],
      correctOption: '23',
    },
    {
      question: 'Multiply 9 by 7.',
      options: ['56', '63', '72', '81'],
      correctOption: '63',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the result of 38 - 17?',
      options: ['22', '20', '21', '19'],
      correctOption: '21',
    },
    {
      question: 'Calculate 4 * 9.',
      options: ['36', '40', '44', '32'],
      correctOption: '36',
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the sum of 56 and 28?',
      options: ['84', '82', '88', '86'],
      correctOption: '84',
    },
    {
      question: 'If Z + 14 = 30, what is the value of Z?',
      options: ['14', '15', '16', '18'],
      correctOption: '16',
    },
  ];
  
  